Finding aid for News and Information Services (University of Michigan) records, 1900-[ongoing]
Bentley Historical Library
- Topical files
  - 1982
    - Affirmative Action Program (Box 84)
    - Afro-American and African Studies (Box 84)
    - Alumni Association (Box 84)
    - Anthropology (Box 84)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of (Box 84)
    - Art, School of (Box 84)
    - Asian Languages and Cultures, Department of (Box 84)
    - Asian Studies (Box 84)
    - Astronomy (LSA) (Box 84)
    - Atmospheric and Oceanic Science (Box 84)
    - Automotive Engineering Lab (Box 84)
    - Biological Station (Box 84)
    - Biology, Department of (Box 84)
    - Biophysics Research Division (Box 84)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 84)
    - Budget (Box 84)
    - Buildings (Box 84)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 85)
    - Cancer Research Institute (Box 85)
    - Career Planning and Placement (Box 85)
    - Chemical Engineering (Box 85)
    - Chemistry (Box 85)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for (Box 85)
    - Civil Engineering (Box 85)
    - Classical Studies (Box 85)
    - Clements, William L. Library (Box 85)
    - Commencement (Box 85)
    - Commission for Women (Box 85)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (Box 85)
    - Committees (Box 85)
    - Communication, Department of (Box 85)
    - Communications, Office of (Box 85)
    - Computing Center (Box 85)
    - Continuing Education of Women, Center for (Box 85)
    - Continuing Legal Education, Institute of (Box 85)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 85)
    - Dental Research Institute (Box 85)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 85)
    - Development and Marketing Communication (Box 85)
    - Development Office (Box 85)
    - Economic Development (Box 85)
    - Economic Development, Center for Research on (Box 85)
    - Economic Outlook Conference (Box 85)
    - Economics (LSA) (Box 85)
    - Education, School of (Box 85)
    - Electrical and Computer Science (Box 85)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 85)
    - English (LSA) (Box 85)
    - English Composition Board (Box 85)
    - English Language Institute (Box 85)
    - Enrollment (Box 85)
    - Environmental and Industrial Health, Institute of (Box 85)
    - Ethics and Religion, Office of (Box 85)
    - Exhibit Museum (Box 85)
    - Extension Service (Box 85)
    - Faculty (Box 85)
    - Fees (Box 85)
    - Financial (Box 85)
    - Financial Aid, Student, Office of (Box 85)
    - Flint College, 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Ford Presidential Library (Box 86)
    - General Counsel (Box 86)
    - Geography (Box 86)
    - Geological Science (Box 86)
    - Germanic Languages and Literature (Box 86)
    - Gerontology, Institute of (Box 86)
    - Government Relations (Box 86)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham School of (Box 86)
    - Great Lakes Research Division (Box 86)
    - Group Dynamics, Center for Research (Box 86)
    - Health Service (Box 86)
    - Higher Education, Center for the Study of (Box 86)
    - History (Box 86)
    - History of Art (Box 86)
    - Hometown Stories (Box 86)
    - Honorary Degrees (Box 86)
    - Honors (Box 86)
    - Faculty (Box 86)
    - Student (Box 86)
    - Honors Council (Box 86)
    - Hopwood Awards (Box 86)
    - Human Adjustment, Institute of (Box 86)
    - Human Growth and Development, Center for (Box 86)
    - Industrial Development Division (Box 86)
    - Industrial and Operations Engineering (Box 86)
    - International Center (Box 86)
    - Inter-University Consortium for Political Research (Box 86)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for (Box 86)
    - Kellogg, W.K. Foundation Institute (Box 86)
    - Kelsey, Museum of Ancient and Medieval Archaeology (Box 86)
    - Kresge Hearing Research Institute (Box 86)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations (Box 86)
    - Law School, 2 folders (Box 86)
    - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on (Box 86)
    - Libraries (Box 86)
    - Library Science, School of (Box 86)
    - Linguistics (Box 86)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of (Box 86)
    - Materials and Metallurgical Engineering (Box 86)
    - Mathematics (LSA) (Box 86)
    - Mechanical Engineering (Box 86)
    - Medical School (Box 86)
    - Mental Retardation and Related Disabilities, Institute for the Study of (Box 86)
    - Michigan Business Review (Box 86)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 86)
    - Michigan Law Review (Box 86)
    - Michigan League (Box 86)
    - Michigan Media Resource Center (Box 86)
    - Michigan Men's Glee Club (Box 86)
    - Michigan Quarterly Review (Box 86)
    - Michigan Union (Box 86)
    - Minority Groups (Box 86)
    - Museum of Anthropology (Box 86)
    - Museum of Art (Box 87)
    - Museum of Paleontology (Box 87)
    - Museum of Zoology (Box 87)
    - Music, School of (Box 87)
    - Natural Resources, School of (Box 87)
    - Near Eastern and North African Studies, Center for (Box 87)
    - Near Eastern Studies (Box 87)
    - News Service (News and Information Services) (Box 87)
    - Nuclear Engineering (Box 87)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 87)
    - Opportunity Award Program (Box 87)
    - Personnel (Box 87)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 87)
    - Philosophy (Box 87)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 87)
    - Physical Education (Box 87)
    - Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation (Box 87)
    - Physics (Box 87)
    - Plant Extension, Plant Operations (Box 87)
    - Poison Control Center (Box 87)
    - Political Science (Box 87)
    - Political Studies, Center for (Box 87)
    - Population Planning, Department of (Box 87)
    - Population Studies Center (Box 87)
    - President, Office of (Box 87)
    - President, National Association (Box 87)
    - Psychology (LSA) (Box 87)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 87)
    - Public Policy Studies, Institute of (Box 87)
    - Public Safety and Security, Department of (Box 87)
    - Recreational Sports (Box 87)
    - Regents (Box 87)
    - Registrar, Office of the (Box 87)
    - Research, Office of the Vice-President for (Box 87)
    - Research Development and Administration, Division of (Box 87)
    - Research Seminar in Quantitative Economics (Box 87)
    - Residential College (Box 87)
    - Romance Languages and Literature (Box 87)
    - ROTC (General) (Box 87)
    - Russel, Henry, Lectures Awards (Box 87)
    - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (Box 87)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of (Box 87)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (Box 87)
    - Senate Assembly (Box 88)
    - Simpson Memorial Institute (Box 88)
    - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 88)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 88)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 88)
    - Sociology (Box 88)
    - South and Southeast Asian Studies, Center for (Box 88)
    - Statistics (Box 88)
    - Student Activities (Box 88)
    - Student Organizations, Office of (Box 88)
    - Student Publications (Box 88)
    - Student Services, Office of (Box 88)
    - Survey Research Center (Box 88)
    - Theater and Drama, Department of (Box 88)
    - Transportation Research Institute (Box 88)
    - University Activities Center (Box 88)
    - University Housing (Box 88)
    - University Musical Society (Box 88)
    - University of Michigan (General) (Box 88)
    - University of Michigan Press (Box 88)
    - Utilization of Scientific Knowledge, Center for Research on (Box 88)
    - Western European Studies, Center for (Box 88)
    - Women-Affirmative Action Program (Box 88)
    - Women's Study Program (Box 88)
    - WUOM (Box 88)
  - 1983
    - Academic Affairs, Office of Vice-President for (Box 89)
    - Aerospace Engineering Department (Box 89)
    - Affirmative Action Program (Box 89)
    - Afroamerican and African Studies, Center for (Box 89)
    - Alumni Association (Box 89)
    - Anthropology (Box 89)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of (Box 89)
    - Art, School of (Box 89)
    - Asian Studies (Box 89)
    - Astronomy (LSA) (Box 89)
    - Atmospheric and Oceanic Science (Box 89)
    - Automotive Engineering Laboratory (Box 89)
    - Biological Sciences (Box 89)
    - Biological Station (Box 89)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 89)
    - Budget (Box 89)
    - Buildings (Box 89)
    - Bush Program in Child Development (Box 89)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 89)
    - Campaign for Michigan (Box 89)
    - Career Planning and Placement (Box 89)
    - Chemical Engineering (Box 89)
    - Chemistry (Box 89)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for (Box 89)
    - Civil Engineering (Box 89)
    - Classical Studies (Box 89)
    - Clements Library, William L. (Box 89)
    - Commencement (Box 89)
    - Commission for Women (Box 89)
    - Communication, Department of (Box 89)
    - Communications, Office of (Box 89)
    - Computing Center (Box 89)
    - Continuing Education of Women, Center for (Box 89)
    - Continuing Legal Education, Institute of (Box 89)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 89)
    - Dentistry, School of (Box 89)
    - Development Office (Box 89)
    - Economic Development, Center for Research on (Box 89)
    - Economic Development-State and Ann Arbor (Box 89)
    - Economic Outlook Conference (Box 89)
    - Economics (Box 89)
    - Education (Box 90)
    - Electrical and Computer Science (Box 90)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 90)
    - English (LSA) (Box 90)
    - English Composition Board (Box 90)
    - English Language Institute (Box 90)
    - Enrollment (Box 90)
    - Ethics and Religion, Office for (Box 90)
    - Exhibit Museum (Box 90)
    - Extension Service (Box 90)
    - Faculty (Box 90)
    - Fees (Box 90)
    - Financial (Box 90)
    - Financial Aid, Student, Office of (Box 90)
    - Flint College (Box 90)
    - Ford Presidential Library (Box 90)
    - Geography (Box 90)
    - Geological Science (Box 90)
    - Germanic Languages and Literature (Box 90)
    - Gerontology, Institute of (Box 90)
    - Government Relations (Box 90)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham School of (Box 90)
    - Great Lakes Research Division (Box 90)
    - Group Dynamics, Center for Research on (Box 90)
    - Health Service (Box 90)
    - Higher Education, Center for Study of (Box 90)
    - History (LSA) (Box 90)
    - History of Art (Box 90)
    - Honors (Box 90)
    - Faculty (Box 90)
    - Student (Box 90)
    - Honors Council (College of LSA) (Box 90)
    - Hopwood Awards (Box 90)
    - Human Adjustment, Institute of (Box 90)
    - Human Growth and Development, Center for (Box 90)
    - Industrial Development Division (Box 90)
    - Intercollegiate Athletics (Rosebowl) (Box 90)
    - International Center (Box 90)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for (Box 90)
    - Kelsey, Museum of Ancient and Medieval Archaeology (Box 90)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations (Box 91)
    - Law School (Box 91)
    - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on (Box 91)
    - Library Science, School of (Box 91)
    - Libraries (Box 91)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of (Box 91)
    - Materials Science and Engineering (Box 91)
    - Mathematics (LSA) (Box 91)
    - Medical School (Box 91)
    - Men's Glee Club (and Women's Glee Club) (Box 91)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (Box 91)
    - Michigan Quarterly Review (Box 91)
    - Michigan Union (Box 91)
    - Minority Groups (Box 91)
    - Museum of Anthropology (Box 91)
    - Museum of Art (Box 91)
    - Museum of Paleontology (Box 91)
    - Museum of Zoology (Box 91)
    - Music, School of (Box 91)
    - Natural Resources, School of (Box 91)
    - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering (Box 91)
    - Near Eastern and North African Studies (Box 91)
    - News and Information Services (Box 91)
    - Nuclear Engineering (Box 91)
    - Personnel (Box 91)
    - Pharmacy, College of (Box 91)
    - Philosophy (Box 91)
    - Phoenix Project (Box 91)
    - Physical Education (Box 91)
    - Physics (Box 91)
    - Plant Extension; plant operation (Box 91)
    - Political Science (Box 91)
    - Political Studies, Center for (Box 91)
    - Population Planning, Center for (Box 91)
    - Population Studies Center (Box 91)
    - President, Office of (Box 91)
    - President, National Association (Box 91)
    - Psychology (LSA) (Box 91)
    - Public Health, School of (Box 91)
    - Public Policy Studies, Institute of (Box 91)
    - Public Safety and Security (Box 91)
    - Recreational Sports (Box 91)
    - Regents (Box 91)
    - Registrar, Office of the (Box 91)
    - Research Development and Administration, Division of (Box 91)
    - Research Seminar in Quantitative Economics (Box 92)
    - Residential College (Box 92)
    - Robotics (Box 92)
    - ROTC (General) (Box 92)
    - Russel, Henry, Lecture Awards (Box 92)
    - Russian and East European Studies, Center for (Box 92)
    - Science and Technology, Institute of (Box 92)
    - Sea Grant Program (Box 92)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (Box 92)
    - Senate Assembly (Box 92)
    - Simpson Memorial Institute (Box 92)
    - Social Research, Institute for (Box 92)
    - Social Work, School of (Box 92)
    - Sociology (Box 92)
    - South and Southeast Asian Studies, Center for (Box 92)
    - Statistics (Box 92)
    - Student Activities (Box 92)
    - Student Organizations, Office of (Box 92)
    - Student Publications (Box 92)
    - Student Services, Office of (Box 92)
    - Survey Research Center (Box 92)
    - Theater and Drama Department (Box 92)
    - Transportation Research Institute (Box 92)
    - University Housing (Box 92)
    - University Musical Society (Box 92)
    - University of Michigan (General) (Box 92)
    - University of Michigan Press (Box 92)
    - University Relations (Box 92)
    - University Theatre Program (Box 92)
    - Western European Studies, Center for (Box 92)
    - Women-Affirmative Action (Box 92)
    - Women's Study Program (Box 92)
    - WUOM Radio Station (Box 92)
  - 1984-1985
    - Academic Affairs, Office of Vice-President for (Box 93)
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Admissions Office
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Aerospace Engineering Department
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Affirmative Action Program
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Afro-American/African Studies
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Alumni Association
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Anthropology
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Architecture and Urban Planning, College of
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Art, School of
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Asian Languages and Cultures (formerly Far Eastern Languages and Literatures)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Asian Studies
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Astronomy (LSA)
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Atmospheric and Oceanic Science
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Biological Sciences (Box 93)
    - Automotive Engineering Laboratory
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Biological Sciences
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Biological Station
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Botanical Gardens
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Budget
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Buildings
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Bush Program in Child Development
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Business Administration, School of
      - 1984 (Box 93)
      - 1985 (Box 93)
    - Campaign for Michigan (Box 94)
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Cancer Research Institute
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Career Planning and Placement
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Chemical Engineering
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Chemistry
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Chinese Studies, Center for
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Civil Engineering
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Classical Studies
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Clements Library, William L.
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Commencement
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Commission for Women
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Committees--University-wide
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Communication, Department of
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Computing Center
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Consumer Attitudes, Survey of
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Continuing Education of Women, Center for the
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Continuing Legal Education, Institute of
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Dearborn Campus
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Dentistry, School of
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Dental Research Institute
      - 1984 (Box 94)
    - Development Office
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Development and Communication, Office of the Vice-President for
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Development and Marketing Communication (formerly University Publications)
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Economic development-State and Ann Arbor
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Economic Development, Center for Research on
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Economic Outlook Conference
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Economics
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Education, School of
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Electrical Engineering and Computer Science
      - 1984 (Box 94)
      - 1985 (Box 94)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 95)
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - English (LSA)
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - English Composition Board
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - English Language Institute
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Enrollment
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Ethics and Religion, Office for
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Exhibit Museum
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Extension Service
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Faculty
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Fees
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Financial
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Financial Aid, Student, Office of
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Flint College
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Ford Presidential Library
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - General Counsel
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Geography
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Geological Science
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Germanic Languages and Literature
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Gerontology, Institute of
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Government Relations
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Graduate Studies, Horace H. Rackham School of
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Great Lakes and Marine Waters Center
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Great Lakes Research Division
      - 1984 (Box 95)
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Group Dynamics, Research Center for
      - 1985 (Box 95)
    - Higher Education, Center for Study of (Box 96)
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - History (LSA)
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - History of Art
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Hometown Stories
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Honors (Box 96)
    - Faculty
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Student
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Honors Council
      - 1984 (Box 96)
    - Hopwood Awards
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Human Growth and Development, Center for
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Industrial Development Division
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Industrial and Operations Engineering
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Information Technology
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Inter-University Consortium for Political Research
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - International Center
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Kellogg, W.K., Foundation Institute
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Kelsey, Museum of Ancient and Medieval Archaeology
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Kresge Hearing Research Institute
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Labor and Industrial Relations
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Law School
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Libraries
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Library Science, School of
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Linguistics
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Literature, Science and the Arts, College of
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Materials Science and Engineering, Department of
      - 1984 (Box 96)
    - Mathematics (LSA)
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Mechanical Engineering
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 96)
    - Medical School
      - 1984 (Box 96)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Mental Health Research Institute
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Michigan Historical Collections
      - 1984 (Box 97)
    - Michigan Law Review
      - 1984 (Box 97)
    - Michigan League
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Michigan Media Resource Center
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Michigan Men's Glee Club (and Women's)
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Michigan Quarterly Review
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Michigan Union
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Museum of Anthropology
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Museum of Art
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Museum of Paleontology
      - 1984 (Box 97)
    - Museum of Zoology
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Music, School of
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Natural Resources, School of
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Naval Architecture and Marine Engineering
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Near Eastern and North African Studies
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - News and Information Services
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Nuclear Engineering
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Nursing, School of
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Occupational Safety and Environmental Health
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Personnel
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Pharmacy, College of
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Philosophy
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Phoenix Project
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Physical Education
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Physics
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Planning and Marketing
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Plant Extension; plant operation
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Political Science
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Political Studies, Center for
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Population Planning, Center for
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - Population Studies Center
      - 1984 (Box 97)
      - 1985 (Box 97)
    - President, Office of (Box 98)
      - 1984 (Box 98)
      - 1985 (Box 98)
    - President, National Association
      - 1984 (Box 98)
      - 1985 (Box 98)
    - Psychology (LSA)
      - 1984 (Box 98)
      - 1985 (Box 98)
    - Public Health, School of
      - 1984 (Box 98)